A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Special Studies Project, RG 4 FA387
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Studies Project, 1956-1964; 4; 28 Cubic Feet 70 boxes
  - Subpanel V: United States Utilization of Human Resources, 1956-1964; E
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Transcript, 1957 April 11-12 (Box 39, Folder 435)
    - Report Drafts - General Material, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 436)
    - Report Drafts - Hechinger, Fred, 1957 April 3 (Box 39, Folder 437)
    - Report Drafts - Outline, Points to Cover, 1957 April 11-12 (Box 39, Folder 438)
    - Report Drafts - No Author Given, 1957 April 16 (Box 39, Folder 439)
    - Report Drafts - Lindsay, Franklin A., 1957 April 25 (Box 39, Folder 440)
    - Report Drafts - Hechinger, Fred, 1957 April 28 (Box 39, Folder 441)
    - Report Drafts - Summary, 1957 May 4 (Box 40, Folder 442)
    - Report Drafts - Haskins, Caryl P., 1957 August 20 (Box 40, Folder 443)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 September 16, 23 (Box 40, Folder 444)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 October 21 (Box 40, Folder 445)
    - Report Drafts - Gardner, John W. - Draft - Comments Compiled, 1958 February 4 (Box 40, Folder 446)
    - Report Drafts - Gardner, John W., 1958 February 26, March 17 (Box 40, Folder 447)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1958 March 25 (Box 40, Folder 448)
    - Report Drafts - Ginzberg, Eli - "Military Manpower" Section, 1958 May 23 (Box 40, Folder 449)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1958 March 31 (Box 40, Folder 450)
    - Report Drafts - Gardner, John W., 1958 April 3 (Box 40, Folder 451)
    - Report Drafts - Draft of April 16, 1958 - Comments Compiled, 1958 April 16 (Box 40, Folder 452)
    - Report Drafts - Draft of April 16, 1958 (Revised Version) - Comments Compiled, 1958 April 16 (Box 40, Folder 453)
    - Report Drafts - Draft of June 11, 1958, 11 June 1958 (Box 40, Folder 454)
    - Report Endorsements, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 455)
    - Report - Public Release Copy, 1958 June 23 (Box 41, Folder 456)
    - Report Summary - Drafts and Public Release Copy, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 457)
    - Report - Press Coverage, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 458)
    - Report - Press Release, 1958 June 23 (Box 41, Folder 459)
    - Report - Printed Copy, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 460)
  - Subpanel VI: United States Democratic Process, 1956-1964; F
    - Organization - Issues and Scope of Report, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 461)
    - Organization - Membership, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 462)
    - Organization - Dissolution, 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 463)
    - Membership - Clay, Lucius D., 1956-1961 (Box 41, Folder 464)
    - Membership - Dart, Justin, 1956-1961 (Box 41, Folder 465)
    - Membership - Dickey, John S., 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 466)
    - Membership - Dickey, John S., 1958-1962 (Box 42, Folder 467)
    - Membership - Goodpaster, Andrew J., 1956-1961 (Box 42, Folder 468)
    - Membership - Harrison, Wallace K., 1956-1961 (Box 42, Folder 469)
    - Membership - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1956-1961 (Box 42, Folder 470)
    - Membership - Percy, Charles, 1956-1958 (Box 42, Folder 471)
    - Membership - Percy, Charles, 1958-1961 (Box 42, Folder 472)
    - Membership - Pike, James A., 1956-1961 (Box 42, Folder 473)
    - Membership - Price, Don K., 1956-1961 (Box 42, Folder 474)
    - Membership - Thomson, Charles A. H., 1956-1962 (Box 42, Folder 475)
    - Papers - Organization, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 476)
    - Papers - Elliott, William Y. - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 477)
    - Papers - Elliott, William Y. - Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 43, Folder 478)
    - Papers - Elliott, William Y. - Paper VI-1 - "A Moral Basis for the Foreign Policy of the U.S.", 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 479)
    - Papers - Kintner, William R. - Paper VI-2 - "Executive Branch Organization...", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 480)
    - Papers - Elliott, William Y. - Paper VI-3 - "Integration of Presidential Control of Foreign Policy", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 481)
    - Papers - Elliott, William Y. - Paper VI-3a - "Improving the Executive's Relations With Congress...", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 482)
    - Papers - Bailey, Stephen K. - Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 43, Folder 483)
    - Papers - Bailey, Stephen K. - Paper VI-5 - "Executive-Legislative Relations...", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 484)
    - Papers - Smithies, Arthur - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - Papers - Smithies, Arthur - Paper VI-6 - "The Role of Budgetary Process...", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 486)
    - Papers - Bonesteel, C. H. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 43, Folder 487)
    - Papers - Bonesteel, C. H. - Paper VI-7 - "The Making of Timely, Long Range Strategic Decisions", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 488)
    - Papers - Halaby, N. E. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 43, Folder 489)
    - Papers - Halaby, N. E. - Paper VI-8 - "The U.S. Strategic Planning Process", 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 490)
    - Papers - Warren, Avra - Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 44, Folder 491)
    - Papers - Warren, Avra - Paper VI-9 - "American Foreign Relations...", 1956-1958 (Box 44, Folder 492)
    - Papers - Sayre, Wallace S. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 44, Folder 493)
    - Papers - Hilsman, Roger - Paper VI-11 - "Congressional-Executive Relations and Foreign Policy", 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 494)
    - Papers - Miles, Arnold - Paper VI-12 - "Administrative Trends... Foreign Affairs", 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 495)
    - Meetings - Organization, 1956-1960 (Box 44, Folder 496)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1956 November 21 (Box 44, Folder 497)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Organizational Records, Minutes, Transcripts, 1957 January 22 (Box 44, Folder 498)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Organizational Records, Minutes, Transcript, 1957 February 20 (Box 44, Folder 499)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Organizational Records, Minutes, Transcript, 1957 March 28 (Box 44, Folder 500)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 5 - Organizational Records, Minutes, Transcript, 1957 May 1 (Box 44, Folder 501)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 6 - Organizational Records, Minutes, Transcript, 1957 May 20 (Box 45, Folder 502)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 7 - Organizational Records, 1958 March 8 (Box 45, Folder 503)
    - Report Drafts - General Material, 1957-1958 (Box 45, Folder 504)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H. - Outlines, 1957 March 25, 28 (Box 45, Folder 505)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H., 1957 April 9, 25 (Box 45, Folder 506)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H., 1957 May 4 (Box 45, Folder 507)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H., 1957 May 26 (Box 45, Folder 508)
    - Report Drafts - Rostow, Walt, 1957 June 12 (Box 45, Folder 509)
    - Report Drafts - Elliott, William Y., 1957 June 19, 24 (Box 45, Folder 510)
    - Report Drafts - Rostow, Walt, 1957 July 5 (Box 45, Folder 511)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H., 1957 July 11 (Box 45, Folder 512)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H. - Comments by Kissinger and Elliott, 1957 July 11 (Box 46, Folder 513)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 July 22 (Box 46, Folder 514)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight - Comments by Kissinger, 1957 July 22 (Box 46, Folder 515)
    - Report Drafts - Berle, Adolf and Cooke, Dwight, 1957 July 29 (Box 46, Folder 516)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 August 10 (Box 46, Folder 517)
    - Report Drafts - Kintner, John F., 1957 August 20 (Box 46, Folder 518)
    - Report Drafts - Dickey, John S. - "Comments Regarding a Draft Report for Subpanel VI", 1957 October 17 (Box 46, Folder 519)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 November 5 (Box 46, Folder 520)
    - Report Drafts - Dickey, John S. - General Comments, 1957 December 6 (Box 46, Folder 521)
    - Report Drafts - Dickey, John S., 1958 February 26 (Box 46, Folder 522)
    - Report Drafts - Hanks, Nancy - Summary and Recommendations, 1958 February 26 (Box 46, Folder 523)
    - Report Drafts - Comments, 1958 February 26 (Box 47, Folder 524)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert - Introduction, 1958 March 18, 20 (Box 47, Folder 525)
    - Report Drafts - Thomson, Charles A. H., 1958 May 1 (Box 47, Folder 526)
    - Report Drafts - Dickey, John S., 1959 January 26 (Box 47, Folder 527)
    - Report Drafts - Dickey, John S. - Comments, 1960 January 26 (Box 47, Folder 528)
    - Report - Summary, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 529)
    - Report - Manuscript for Printer, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 530)
    - Report - Page Proofs, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 531)
    - Report - Endorsements, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 532)
    - Report - Printed Copy, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 533)
    - Report - Press Copy, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 534)
    - Report - Leatherbound Copies, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 535)
    - Photographs, 1957-1963; 7
      - Robert I. Fleming, circa 1960-1961; 40 prints (1 duplicate) 1 4x5 negative
      - John R. Camp Survey, 1957; 128 color prints
      - John R. Camp Survey - Album 1, 1957; 58 prints
      - Ghana - Poultry Breeding, 1960 December; 13 prints
      - Ghana - Water Project - Pakre Dam, 1959; 30 prints
      - Ghana - Water Project - Pakre Dam, 1959 December; 39 prints
      - Electrical Assembly Project, 1962; 4 prints
      - Nigeria - Housing, 1959; 4 prints (1 color)
      - Iron and Steel, 1959-1962; 21 prints 1 8x10 negative
      - Nigeria - Textiles, 1963 March; 2 prints
      - Wiilliam M. Dietel, 1 print
      - Staff, 1 print
  - Subpanel VII: The Moral Framework of National Purpose, 1956-1964; G
    - Organization - Members, Statement of Problems, Dissolution, 1957-1960 (Box 48, Folder 536)
    - Membership - Calhoun, Robert L., 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 537)
    - Membership - Faust, Clarence H., 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 538)
    - Membership - Finkelstein, Louis, 1956-1962 (Box 48, Folder 539)
    - Membership - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 540)
    - Membership - Johnson, Ernest F., 1957-1962 (Box 48, Folder 541)
    - Membership - McKeon, Richard P., 1956-1961 (Box 48, Folder 542)
    - Membership - La Farge, John, 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 543)
    - Membership - Mac Iver, R. M., 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 544)
    - Membership - Murray, John Courtney, 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 545)
    - Papers - Organization, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 546)
    - Papers - Mc Keon, Richard - Paper VII-1 - "Responsibility as Sign and as Instrumentality", 1957 (Box 48, Folder 547)
    - Papers - Mc Keon, Richard - Paper VII-2 - "Human Values and Technology", 1957 (Box 48, Folder 548)
    - Papers - La Farge, John - "Moral Issues of Urbanization", 1957 (Box 48, Folder 549)
    - Meetings - Organization, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Organizational Records, 1957 March 11 (Box 49, Folder 551)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Organizational Records, 1957 April 8 (Box 49, Folder 552)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Transcript, 1957 April 8 (Box 49, Folder 553)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Organizational Records, 1957 April 29 (Box 49, Folder 554)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Transcript, 1957 April 29 (Box 49, Folder 555)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Organizational Records, 1957 May 20 (Box 49, Folder 556)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Transcript, 1957 May 20 (Box 49, Folder 557)
    - Report Drafts - General Material, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 558)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 April 26, June 6 (Box 49, Folder 559)
    - Report Drafts - Johnson and Cooke - Comments, 1957 June 6 (Box 49, Folder 560)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 July 1, 16 (Box 49, Folder 561)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert - Comments by Kissinger, Free, Cantril, 1957 July 16 (Box 49, Folder 562)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert - Comments by Kintner, Nelson Rockefeller, Cooke, 1957 July 26 (Box 49, Folder 563)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 August 16 (Box 49, Folder 564)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert - Comments, 1957 August 16 (Box 49, Folder 565)
  - Subpanels VI and VII Joint Report-Writing Committee, 1956-1964; H
    - Report Writing Committee - Background Material, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 566)
    - Report Writing Committee - Consultants (F-W), 1960 (Box 50, Folder 567)
    - Report Writing Committee - Organization, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 568)
    - Report Writing Committee (Members) - Bryson, Luman, 1956-1959 (Box 50, Folder 569)
    - Report Writing Committee (Members) - Frankel, Charles, 1960-1963 (Box 50, Folder 570)
    - Report Writing Committee (Members) - Galantiere, Lewis, 1959-1962 (Box 50, Folder 571)
    - Report Writing Committee (Members) - Hecksher, August, 1956-1962 (Box 50, Folder 572)
    - Report Writing Committee (Members) - Herring, Pendleton, 1956-1963 (Box 50, Folder 573)
    - Report Writing Committee (Members) - Perkins, James, 1956-1964 (Box 50, Folder 574)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 1 - Organizational Records, 1960 January 22 (Box 51, Folder 575)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 2 - Tape Transcription, 1960 January 27 (Box 51, Folder 576)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 3 - Tape Transcription, 1960 February 4 (Box 51, Folder 577)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 4 - Tape Transcription, 1960 February 9 (Box 51, Folder 578)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 5 - Tape Transcription, 1960 March 14 (Box 51, Folder 579)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 6 - Tape Transcription, 1960 March 15 (Box 51, Folder 580)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meeting No. 7, 1960 March 29 (Box 51, Folder 581)
    - Report Writing Committee (Meetings) - Meetings Nos. 8 & 9, 1960 April 11, 22 (Box 51, Folder 582)
    - Report Writing Committee (Report Drafts) - Galantiere, Lewis - Various Drafts, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 583)
    - Report Writing Committee (Report Drafts) - Frankel, Charles - Various Drafts - 1960 (Box 52, Folder 584)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Draft of March 23, 1960 - Comments, 1960 March 23 (Box 52, Folder 585)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Draft of April 19, 1960, 1960 April 19 (Box 52, Folder 586)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Draft of April 29, 1960, 1960 April 29 (Box 52, Folder 587)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Frankel, Charles, 1960 May 6 (Box 53, Folder 588)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Frankel, 1960 May 11 (Box 53, Folder 589)
      Revised June 17, 1960
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Frankel, Charles - Comments - May 11, 1960, 1960 May 11 (Box 53, Folder 590)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Galantiere, Lewis, 1960 May 23 (Box 53, Folder 591)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Draft of June 22, 1960 - Comments, 1960 June 22 (Box 53, Folder 592)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report Drafts - Frankel, Charles - Comments, 1960 July 20 (Box 54, Folder 593)
    - Report Writing Committee - Report - Summary for Pamphlet, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 594)
  - Overall Panel, 1956-1964; I
    - Organization - Authors, Membership, Major Issues, 1956-1959 (Box 54, Folder 595)
    - Membership - Minton, Lee W., 1956-1961 (Box 54, Folder 596)
    - Papers, 1956, undated (Box 54, Folder 597)
    - Papers - Dickey, John S. - Paper A-1 - "...Great Issues of the Future", 1956 (Box 54, Folder 598)
    - Papers - Berle, Adolf - Paper A-2 - "Thoughts on the Future", 1956 (Box 54, Folder 599)
    - Papers - Sarnoff, David - Paper A-3 - Five Pamphlets, 1955-1956 (Box 54, Folder 600)
    - Papers - Finkelstein, Louis - Paper A-5 - "American Values and ...Foreign Policy", 1957 (Box 54, Folder 601)
    - Papers - Free, Lloyd and Cantril, Hadley - Paper A-6 - "U.S. International Objectives...", 1957 (Box 54, Folder 602)
    - Meetings - Procedures, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 603)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Organization, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 604)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Organization, Minutes, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 605)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Transcript, 1957 March 19-20 (Box 54, Folder 606)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Organization, Records, Minutes, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 607)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Transcript, 1957 May 6-7 (Box 55, Folder 608)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Organization, Records, Minutes, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 609)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Transcript, 1957 June 19 (Box 55, Folder 610)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 5 - Organization, Records, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 611)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 6 - Organization, Records, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 612)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 6 - Transcripts, 1958 February 11-12 (Box 55, Folder 613)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 7 - Organization, Records, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 614)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 8 - Organization, Records, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 615)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 8 - Transcripts, 1958 April 7 (Box 55, Folder 616)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 9 - Organization, Records, 1958 May 21 (Box 55, Folder 617)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 10 - Transcript, 1959 September 17 (Box 55, Folder 618)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 10 - Organization, Records, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 619)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 11 - Organization, Records, 1960 May 17 (Box 56, Folder 620)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 11 - Transcript, 1960 May 17 (Box 56, Folder 621)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 12 - Administrative Records, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 622)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 12 - Transcripts, 1960 October 5 (Box 56, Folder 623)
    - Report Drafts - General Material, 1957-1960 (Box 56, Folder 624)
    - Report Drafts - Outlines, 1957 January 24, November 26 (Box 56, Folder 625)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 1 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 August 2, 7 (Box 56, Folder 626)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 1 - Kissinger, Henry and Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 August 27-November 14 (Box 56, Folder 627)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 1 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 October 29- 1958 January 14 (Box 56, Folder 628)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 2 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 August 21 (Box 56, Folder 629)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 2 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 September 3-11 (Box 56, Folder 630)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 2 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November (Box 57, Folder 631)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 2 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 November (Box 57, Folder 632)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 2 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1958 January 13 (Box 57, Folder 633)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 3 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 August-September (Box 57, Folder 634)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 3 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 September 14 (Box 57, Folder 635)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 3 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November 11 (Box 57, Folder 636)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 3 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 November (Box 57, Folder 637)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 3 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1958 January 14 (Box 57, Folder 638)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 4 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 November 12 (Box 57, Folder 639)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 4 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November 15 (Box 57, Folder 640)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 4 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 November 21 (Box 57, Folder 641)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 4 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1958 January 13 (Box 57, Folder 642)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 4 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 September 28 (Box 57, Folder 643)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 5 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 November 25 (Box 57, Folder 644)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 6 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 October 15 (Box 57, Folder 645)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 6 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 November (Box 57, Folder 646)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 6 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 December 2 (Box 57, Folder 647)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 7 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 September 13 (Box 58, Folder 648)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 7 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 December 16 (Box 58, Folder 649)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 8 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 December 19-1958 February 3 (Box 58, Folder 650)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 9 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1958 January 20 (Box 58, Folder 651)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 10 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1958 January 27 (Box 58, Folder 652)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 11 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 October 3 (Box 58, Folder 653)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 12 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 October (Box 58, Folder 654)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 14 - Berle, Adolf, 1957 July 17 (Box 58, Folder 655)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 14 - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 September 3, 9 (Box 58, Folder 656)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 15 - Barnett, Lincoln, 1957 November 6 (Box 58, Folder 657)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 17 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November 18 (Box 58, Folder 658)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 18 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November 25 (Box 58, Folder 659)
    - Report Drafts - Chapter 19 - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 December 2 (Box 58, Folder 660)
    - Report Drafts - Introduction to Part III - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November 22-1958 January 20 (Box 58, Folder 661)
    - Report Drafts - Introduction - Comments, 1960 September 22 (Box 58, Folder 662)
    - Report Drafts - Preface Outline - Kissinger, Henry, 1960 October 2 (Box 58, Folder 663)
    - Report Drafts - Preface - Hughes, Emmet J., 1960 October 4 (Box 58, Folder 664)
    - Report Drafts - Preface Outline - Kissinger, Henry, 1960 October 5 (Box 58, Folder 665)
    - Report Drafts - Preface and Introduction - Kissinger, Henry, 1960 October 25 (Box 58, Folder 666)
    - Report Drafts - Preface and Introduction - Gardner, John - Comments, 1960 October 31 (Box 58, Folder 667)
    - Report Drafts - Preface - Comments, 1960 November 5, 11 (Box 58, Folder 668)
      Comments by Emmet J. Hughes, Louis Galantiere, and John Gardner.
    - Report Drafts - Introduction - Ruebhausen, Oscar - Comments, 1960 November 14 (Box 58, Folder 669)
    - Report Drafts - Preface and Introduction - Comments, 1960 November 16 (Box 58, Folder 670)
    - Report Drafts - Preface - Reubhausen, Oscar, 1960 November 21 (Box 58, Folder 671)
    - Report Drafts - Preface - Reubhausen, Oscar - Comments, 1960 November 22 (Box 58, Folder 672)
    - Report - Preface and Introduction, 1960 November 29 (Box 58, Folder 673)
    - Report - Endorsements, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 674)
  - Office Reference and Report Publication Files, 1956-1960; J; 5 Cubic Feet 12 boxes
    This subseries includes card files, galley proofs, sets of meeting notes, summaries and transcripts, and subpanel working documents, including texts of reports.
    - Papers I-1 through I-3 (Box 59, Folder 0674A)
    - Papers I-4 through I-6 (Box 59, Folder 675)
    - Papers I-7 through I-8 (Box 59, Folder 676)
    - Papers I-11 through I-16 (Box 59, Folder 677)
    - Papers I-19 through I-20 (Box 59, Folder 678)
    - Papers I-21 through I-25 (Box 59, Folder 679)
    - Papers I-26 through I-29 (Box 60, Folder 680)
    - Papers I-30 through I-31a (Box 60, Folder 681)
    - Papers I-32 through I-36 (Box 60, Folder 682)
    - Papers I-38 through I-40 and Paper I-42 (Box 60, Folder 683)
    - Papers A-1 through A-6 (Box 61, Folder 684)
    - Paper II-2 and Papers II-4 through II-8 (Box 61, Folder 685)
    - Draft Report - Subpanel I - Nelson Rockefeller Copy, 1957 April 5 - May 18 (Box 61, Folder 686)
    - Papers II-10 through II-14 and Papers II-A through II-D (Box 61, Folder 687)
    - Subpanel II Report - Nelson Rockefeller Copy (Box 62, Folder 688)
    - Papers III-1 through III-2 and Papers III-4 through III-8 (Box 62, Folder 689)
    - Papers III-10 through III-14 and Paper III-A (Box 62, Folder 690)
    - Subpanel III Draft Report - Nelson Rockefeller Copy (Box 63, Folder 691)
    - Papers IV-1 through IV-8 (Box 63, Folder 692)
    - Papers IV-9 through IV-10 and Papers IV-12 through IV-19 (Box 63, Folder 693)
    - Subpanel IV - Draft Report - Nelson Rockefeller Copy (Box 64, Folder 694)